{
"question": "ベッド",
"answer": "ベッド"
},
{
"question": "パン",
"answer": "パン"
},
{
"question": "ナイフ",
"answer": "ナイフ"
},
{
"question": "シャツ",
"answer": "シャツ"
},
{
"question": "ネクタイ",
"answer": "ネクタイ"
},
{
"question": "ギター",
"answer": "ギター"
},
{
"question": "セーター",
"answer": "セーター"
},
{
"question": "米",
"answer": "メートル"
},
{
"question": "アパート",
"answer": "アパート"
},
{
"question": "ポケット",
"answer": "ポケット"
},
{
"question": "バター",
"answer": "バター"
},
{
"question": "キロ",
"answer": "キロ"
},
{
"question": "スカート",
"answer": "スカート"
},
{
"question": "レコード",
"answer": "レコード"
},
{
"question": "エレベーター",
"answer": "エレベーター"
},
{
"question": "ズボン",
"answer": "ズボン"
},
{
"question": "ポスト",
"answer": "ポスト"
},
{
"question": "コピー",
"answer": "コピー"
},
{
"question": "シャワー",
"answer": "シャワー"
},
{
"question": "ハンカチ",
"answer": "ハンカチ"
},
